<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MedBLG - InfoSec Enthusiast | Dev - DevOps - AI</title>
    <link>https://medblg.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MedBLG - InfoSec Enthusiast | Dev - DevOps - AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 23:15:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://medblg.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fear the EAR Vuln</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/fear-the-ear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 23:15:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/fear-the-ear/</guid>
      <description>Intro: It has been a while since my last blog post, and here we go again. This one will cover a vulnerability I discovered and reported back in April to a private program in HackerOne which I cannot disclose the name, but it is a well known insurance company in the USA.
In short I have not set and prepare for this finding as I am so busy recently with my full time job, nevertheless I spend some of my spare time on my hobby, including research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struts your way into Strongkey [RCE]</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/strongkey-rce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 16:38:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/strongkey-rce/</guid>
      <description>Intro: Back to Feb 1, 2020 at 5:53PM, I reported a critical vulnerability issue that gives me a remote code execution(RCE) on StrongKey company. To those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, StrongAuth, or StrongKey is a security based company that &amp;ldquo;makes data breach irrelevant, with StrongKey technology, your data becomes worthless to hackers&amp;rdquo; as stated on their website !.
About the company by CyberDb : StrongAuth, Inc. is a Silicon Valley company focused on Symmetric Key Management, Encryption, Tokenization and PKI and FIDO-based Strong-Authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From academic research to LFD critical vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/lfi-is-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 12:46:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/lfi-is-calling/</guid>
      <description>Vulnerable discovered code LFI Intro: Three years ago, while conducting my academic research. I come accross a website to download an interresting pdf course.
I downloaded the pdf, and as always, the nerd come back to mind whenever had the chance, even if it’s not the subject of my research. So, I tried to test the website for what it seems to me a vulnerability. And guess what? it’s a critical one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 09:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/about/</guid>
      <description>$ Whoami Mohamed BAL-GHAUI, a Biomedical Engineer HIT, a PhD student and an InfoSec enthusiast by heart white-hat hacker say! on my spare time I help companies secure their assets, actually your online data. On the Internet, I go by the pseudo name s1m0x1!
This blog is live so to document my infosec journey, solve CTFs (if have time), and share my own ideas and experiences, and especially keep a good journaling habit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating some stuff with jq and bash</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/linux/automate-bash-jq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 16:04:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/linux/automate-bash-jq/</guid>
      <description>Intro: Hi, It has been a while since my last story. This one isn’t going to tell anything special about infosec, in fact nothing with that topic in here. I will be presenting how I managed to automate a task with a malformed json data, especially updating repetitive values for the same key. Let’s start: I won’t go through fundamentals, but some specific parameters will be mentioned here. Yesterday, I got some json data that was like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside a global leader in CyberSecurity [bitdefender dashboard]</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/bxss-bitdefender/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 01:06:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/bxss-bitdefender/</guid>
      <description>How I was able to access one of the russian antivirus (Bitdefender) domains through blind xss !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first steps into the Linux world 3</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 23:10:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro3/</guid>
      <description>What is the best Linux distro and for what? It’s a Linux myth question, though the response can easily find its way from the question. What are you willing to do with ? It’s really depends on what would be your engagement towards the OS (the uses). Are you using it just for daily browsing. For games, Programming and development stuff. Staring without doing anything ? Why not, it could be :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first steps into the Linux world 2</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 23:09:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro2/</guid>
      <description>Why I use Linux ? It’s a great question. Almost every colleagues, friends that had chance to see me work with, keep asking why use it instead of Windows ?. Why getting things complexes ?. To be honest, it’s a matter of taste and how things should be done. (I have no problem with Windows, except security concern). For me I was experiencing Microsoft Windows since the XP version at the age of 11 year-old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first steps into the Linux world 1</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 23:08:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/linux/intro/</guid>
      <description>Tux Logo Intro: Hello, I wish I found you all well. I’m gonna to make some notes about my experience with Linux, it has been till now almost one year using it officially. A powerful operation system. I had always the idea to learn something new, different to increase in somehow creativity, and efficiency. This write up will be divided into three sections, in which I will describe my learning curve with Linux, and of course other stuff as well without digging into details to avoid overwhelming the reader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juicy Infos hidden in js scripts leads to RCE</title>
      <link>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/juicy-js-rce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 08:00:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://medblg.top/post/bugs/juicy-js-rce/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for the late, I wasn’t able to write this before. Academic exams were overwhelming as usual. Now, I got some time. Let’s start the (story)! One day, while doing my research as usual, I come across a web application that I (want) to test. Just curious, you know when a website pop up and you as usual with your hacker mind spirit want to test, just a small check list will be enough (as it wasn’t your target at first place).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
